thecoupongirl.com 2012-11-22

# Privacy Policy — The Coupon Girl

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to [contact me](http://thecoupongirl.com/contact).

At TheCouponGirl.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by TheCouponGirl.com and how it is used.

### **Log Files**

Like many other Web sites, TheCouponGirl.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet  
Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

### **Cookies and Web Beacons**

TheCouponGirl.com does not use cookies.

### DoubleClick DART Cookie

.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on TheCouponGirl.com.  
.:: Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to TheCouponGirl.com and other sites on the Internet.  
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include ....

  * Google Adsense
  * Commission Junction
  * Linkshare
  * Amazon

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on TheCouponGirl.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive  
your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

TheCouponGirl.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. TheCouponGirl.com privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.

### Collection of Information

When visiting TheCouponGirl.com, the IP address used to access the site will be logged along with the dates and times of access. This information is purely used to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement and gather broad demographic information for internal use. Most importantly, any recorded IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

There will also be times where other information is needed in order to fulfill the requirements of a giveaway if you are chosen as the winner. TheCouponGirl.com will NEVER sell your information and the only time your information will be shared is if a giveaway sponsor is in possession of the prize and needs your information in order to ship said prize to you.

### **Links to Third Party Websites**

TheCouponGirl.com strives to bring ethical deals to you and sometimes in order to obtain deals credit to third party sites has to be given. TheCouponGirl.com cannot be held liable for the content and/or privacy policy of a third party website. TheCouponGirl.com does not endorse any site that teaches incorrect couponing methods and strives not to include such websites.
